<fdb>
    <!-- NOIR -->
    <perfume>
        <title>OUD NOIR INTENSE</title>
        <thumbnail>noir_100ml</thumbnail>
        <themecolor>#c8000000</themecolor>
        <perfumer>FRANÇOIS MERLE-BAUDOIN</perfumer>
        <topnotes>Bergamot, Cardamom</topnotes>
        <middlenotes>Rose, Jasmin</middlenotes>
        <basenotes>Sandalwood, Saffron, Patchouli, Vanilla, Musk, Amber</basenotes>
        <fontcolor>#c8000000</fontcolor>
        <portrait>perfumer8</portrait>
        <profile>Born in Grasse, France, François is a fifth generation French perfumer – his grandfather created the world-renowned Anaïs Anaïs. He brings a wealth of experience from a career spanning more than 25 years, and has been a guiding light in his tenures at SARL Creative Scents andSARL Creations and Parfums.</profile>

        <cwx>590</cwx>
        <cwy>590</cwy>
    </perfume>

    <!-- blue -->
    <perfume>
        <title>OUD BLUE INTENSE</title>
        <thumbnail>blue_100ml</thumbnail>
        <themecolor>#c8006488</themecolor>
        <perfumer>GUILLAUME FLAVIGNY</perfumer>
        <topnotes>Cardamom, Nutmeg, Mandarin</topnotes>
        <middlenotes>Frankincense, Ciste, Myrrh Essence, Amber</middlenotes>
        <basenotes>Opoponax Resinoid, Myrrh, Resinoid, Styrax, Benzoin</basenotes>
        <fontcolor>#c8ffffff</fontcolor>
        <portrait>perfumer1</portrait>
        <profile>After studying Chemistry, Guillaume enrolled at the ISIPCA (Institut Supérieur International du Parfum de la Cosmétique et de l’Aromatique Alimentaire). In 1998, following his dream to enter the world of perfumery, he joined in the promotion of MST ISIPCA’s Bel Aesthète. With a desire to broaden his knowledge and further develop his creativity, Guillaume then studied at the Givaudan School of Perfumery, and in 2003, at the age of 27, joined the Fine Fragrance team of Perfumers at Givaudan, Paris.</profile>
        <cwx>782</cwx>
        <cwy>978</cwy>
    </perfume>

    <!-- ORANGE -->
    <perfume>
        <title>OUD ORANGE INTENSE</title>
        <thumbnail>orange_100ml</thumbnail>
        <themecolor>#c8ff9d1e</themecolor>
        <perfumer>CAROLINE SABAS</perfumer>
        <topnotes>Coconut, Fruits</topnotes>
        <middlenotes>Vanilla Bourbon</middlenotes>
        <basenotes>Vanilla, Musk</basenotes>
        <fontcolor>#c8000000</fontcolor>
        <portrait>perfumer7</portrait>
        <profile>Born in Cannes, France, Caroline studied at the prestigious from ISIPCA (Institut Supérieur International du Parfum de la Cosmétique et de l’Aromatique Alimentaire) in Versailles for two years, and finished her studies at Chanel in Paris before officially becoming a perfumer.  She joined Fragrance Resources in New York in 1997, before coming to Givaudan in 2003.</profile>
        <cwx>374</cwx>
        <cwy>190</cwy>
    </perfume>

    <!-- JAUNE -->
    <perfume>
        <title>OUD JAUNE INTENSE</title>
        <thumbnail>jaune_100ml</thumbnail>
        <themecolor>#c8fee300</themecolor>
        <perfumer>NATHALIE CETTO</perfumer>
        <topnotes>Monoi, Ylang Ylang, Pineapple, Water Fruits</topnotes>
        <middlenotes>Jasmin, Orange Blossom, White Flowers, Salicylate</middlenotes>
        <basenotes>Lactonic, Vanilla, Musk</basenotes>
        <fontcolor>#c8000000</fontcolor>
        <portrait>perfumer5</portrait>
        <profile>Nathalie grew up in Grasse, and after receiving a doctorate in Pharmaceuticals, she followed her passion for fragrances, enrolling at the Givaudan School of Perfumery. At the age of 29, she joined the team of Fine Fragrance perfumers in Paris. Her enthusiasm, creativity, and expertise have brought a new dimension to Fragrance Du Bois’ most optimistic fragrance.</profile>

        <cwx>180</cwx>
        <cwy>400</cwy>
    </perfume>

    <!-- ROUGE -->
    <perfume>
        <title>OUD ROUGE INTENSE</title>
        <thumbnail>rouge_100ml</thumbnail>
        <themecolor>#c8a2202a</themecolor>
        <perfumer>GUILLAUME FLAVIGNY</perfumer>
        <topnotes>Lemon, Pink Pepper</topnotes>
        <middlenotes>Cedarwood, Patchouli, Sandalwood</middlenotes>
        <basenotes>Musk</basenotes>
        <fontcolor>#c8000000</fontcolor>
        <portrait>perfumer2</portrait>
        <profile>After studying Chemistry, Guillaume enrolled at the ISIPCA (Institut Supérieur International du Parfum de la Cosmétique et de l’Aromatique Alimentaire). In 1998, following his dream to enter the world of perfumery, he joined in the promotion of MST ISIPCA’s Bel Aesthète. With a desire to broaden his knowledge and further develop his creativity, Guillaume then studied at the Givaudan School of Perfumery, and in 2003, at the age of 27, joined the Fine Fragrance team of Perfumers at Givaudan, Paris.</profile>
        <cwx>610</cwx>
        <cwy>146</cwy>
    </perfume>

    <!-- ROSE -->
    <perfume>
        <title>OUD ROSE INTENSE</title>
        <thumbnail>rose_100ml</thumbnail>
        <themecolor>#c8a80e70</themecolor>
        <perfumer>HAMID MERATI-KASHANI</perfumer>
        <topnotes>Bergamot, Fruit</topnotes>
        <middlenotes>Geranium, Rose, Sandalwood, Amber</middlenotes>
        <basenotes></basenotes>
        <fontcolor>#c8000000</fontcolor>
        <portrait>perfumer3</portrait>
        <profile>Hamid’s interest in perfumery was stimulated by an invitation from family friends to visit a rose plantation in Ghamsar – an ancient city famous for its rose cultivations, and located in the central Iranian desert. Hamid was so fascinated by what he experienced on his visit – the fragrant fields; the spectacle of rose pickers and the distillation process, that a whole new world opened up to him.</profile>
        <cwx>880</cwx>
        <cwy>250</cwy>
    </perfume>

    <!-- VERT -->
    <perfume>
        <title>OUD VERT INTENSE</title>
        <thumbnail>vert_100ml</thumbnail>
        <themecolor>#c80e6e00</themecolor>
        <perfumer>OLIVIER PESCHEUX</perfumer>
        <topnotes>Bergamot, Ginger, Cardamom</topnotes>
        <middlenotes>Coriander Seeds, Nutmeg, Geranium</middlenotes>
        <basenotes>Vetiver, Cedarwood, Musk</basenotes>
        <fontcolor>#c8000000</fontcolor>
        <portrait>perfumer6</portrait>
        <profile>After graduating in 1990 from ISIPCA (Institut Supérieur International duParfum  de la Cosmétique et de l’Aromatique Alimentaire), Olivier was engaged by Parfums Annick Goutal. He joined the Kao Corporation in 1993, and five years later started at Givaudan. Working with Jean Amic, Olivier discovered and developed his love for prestige perfumery, and is passionate about broadening his expertise as well as his horizons.</profile>
        <cwx>220</cwx>
        <cwy>828</cwy>
    </perfume>

    <!-- VIOLET -->
    <perfume>
        <title>OUD VIOLET INTENSE</title>
        <thumbnail>violet_100ml</thumbnail>
        <themecolor>#c86a3d76</themecolor>
        <perfumer>ALEXANDRA KOSINSKI</perfumer>
        <topnotes>Mandarin, Black Pepper, Elemi</topnotes>
        <middlenotes>Frankincense, Tonka Bean, Nutmeg</middlenotes>
        <basenotes>Cistus, Soft Amber, Musk</basenotes>
        <fontcolor>#c8000000</fontcolor>
        <portrait>perfumer4</portrait>
        <profile>Alexandra has dreamt of being a perfumer since the age of twelve. Strong-minded and determined, she studied for her Deug A, at ISIPCA (Institut Supérieur International du Parfum de la Cosmétique et de l’Aromatique Alimentaire) and finished top of her class. She began working at Quest as an assistant perfumer,  before progressing to junior perfumer. Today, Alexandra is fulfilling her life’s ambition as a perfumer at Givaudan.</profile>
        <cwx>1050</cwx>
        <cwy>592</cwy>
    </perfume>


</fdb>